Guide to the Yale University Library Records of Search Committees
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
Yale University Library, records of search committees
1971-1980
RU 746
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
0.5
(2 boxes)
The records consist of resumes, schedules, and notes, documenting the process of hiring of upper level librarians at Yale University Library.
Yale University. Library
General note
Forms part of Yale Record Group 32-H (YRG 32-H), Yale University Library personnel records.
Conditions Governing Access
Access to the records is restricted. See Collection Contents for details.
Scope and Contents
The records consist of resumes, schedules, and notes, documenting the process of hiring of upper level librarians at Yale University Library.
Arrangement
The records are arranged by accession.
Academic libraries; Employee selection; Librarians -- Recruiting; Library personnel management; Yale University -- Employees; Yale University. Library
- Records of search committees, 1971-1980; Accession 1988-A-069
  Conditions Governing Access
  Restricted until Jan 1, 2055.
  - Lipetz, Ben, 1971 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Divinity Librarian Search Committee, 1972 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Comments on Candidates -Associate Librarian for Public Services, 1975 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Candidates for the Position of Associate Librarian for Technical Servies, 1974 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Search Committee for Associate Librarian for Technical Services, 1973-74 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Interview Schedules and Resumes, etc. for Associate Librarian for Public Services, 1975 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Associate Librarian for Public Services, 1975 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Successor to Herman Kahn, 1975 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Medical Librarian Search Committee, 1976 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Liebert, Herman (Fritz), 1972 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Beinecke Librarian Search Committee, 1971-72 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Beinecke Library Search Committee, 1977-78 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - BRBL Director Search Committee, 1977-78 (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - Divinity Librarian Search Committee, 1979 (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - Nesheim, Kenneth, 1980 (Box 2, Folder 15)